<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CollapsingActivity</string>
    <string name="topic_name">WELCOME</string>
    <string name="paragraph">Welcome</string>
    <string name="app">Hello Everyone</string>
    <string name="login">login</string>
    <string name="sign_up">sign up</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="male">male</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="page"> One Piece is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Eiichiro Oda.</string>

    <string name="para">ANIME</string>
    <string name="climax"> One Piece has been serializedin Shueisha
        Weekly Shōnen Jump magazine since July 19, 1997, with the chapters collected into 85 tankōbon volumes to date.
        The story follows the adventures of Monkey D. Luffy, a young man whose body gained the properties of rubber after
        unintentionally eating a Devil Fruit. With his crew of pirates, named the Straw Hat Pirates, Luffy explores the Grand
        Line in search of the world\'s ultimate treasure known as "One Piece" in order to become the next Pirate King.
The manga has been adapted into an original video animation (OVA) produced by Production I.G in 1998, and an anime series
        produced by Toei Animation, which began broadcasting in Japan in 1999. Additionally,
        Toei has developed thirteen animated feature films, one OVA and eleven television specials. Several companies
        have developed various types of merchandising such as a trading card game and numerous video games. The manga series
        was licensed for an English language release in North America and the United Kingdom by Viz Media and in Australia by
        Madman Entertainment. The anime series was licensed by 4Kids Entertainment for an English-language release in North
        America in 2004, before the license was dropped and subsequently acquired by Funimation in 2007.The anime series was licensed by 4Kids Entertainment for an English-language release in North
        America in 2004, before the license was dropped and subsequently acquired by Funimation in 2007.</string>
</resources>
